At last, it has begun...
It has been centuries, and still... the chessboard remains
The black king has not moved at all
He remains seated on his throne
Is it indifference or arrogance behind his inaction?
In five hundred years
I have never forgotten that gaze
When she cast the Curse of Immortality
I saw neither pity nor pleasure in the Ruler of Death's eyes
A Traveler
Arrives here in Snezhnaya after a highly eventful journey through the six other nations
Now, he requests an audience with our god. An offer of an open dialogue
Or does he have ulterior motives?
By collecting the Gnoses
You hope to gain power beyond the level of Cryo Archon?
Once the remains of the Third Descender are no longer scattered across the world...
Only then, we may behold the legacy he sealed away
If we gather enough of these Seals of Life
We might truly be able to defy death after all
When that lady gave this power to my ancestors
Perhaps the contract she made
Was for this purpose
Locked on — no escape!
More where that came from
I don't just sing for me
I sing for every Water Imp whose voice has ever graced this theater
I'm the only one left
I'm the only one
Who can keep these songs alive
Taking the stage
An elegy to mortality
Our love... was spoiled long ago by the Heavenly Principles
Strange...
I sense Pavlina's aura on you
Did she fail after all?
If everyone agrees to remove the seal
A truth laid buried for five hundred years will come to light
In all this time
I've had no great ambition to recover my stolen morsel
But if it were used to extract life
Or even defy death...
It would be a grave transgression
Now... I can kill without further consequence
Snezhnaya
Has lived under the threat of annihilation by a Nail of Retribution at any moment
...Asmoday? You've met her?
The Shades of the Heavenly Principles
Life, Death, Time, and Space
Are ubiquitous
Surely, you don't really think
You have what it takes to face me head on?
I didn't know gods liked to trash-talk their opponents
Whatever the price may be, whatever I must suffer, so be it!
Ronova!!!
It is time to begin the next phase of the plan
It seems I'll have to reclaim what is mine
Care to stop me
Cryo Archon?